<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="en-IN">
  <voice name="en-IN-NeerjaNeural">
    <prosody rate="medium">
      <p>
        Organised crime gangs are now <emphasis>manufacturing their own branded weight-loss drugs</emphasis>.
        <break time="300ms"/>
        These products are meticulously designed to look exactly like legitimate medicines.
        <break time="700ms"/>
      </p>
    </prosody>
  </voice>
  <voice name="en-IN-PrabhatNeural">
    <prosody rate="medium">
      <p>
        The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency, or MHRA, has issued a stark warning.
        <break time="300ms"/>
        They've just conducted the <emphasis>largest single seizure of trafficked weight-loss drugs</emphasis>, highlighting a significant threat to public health.
        <break time="750ms"/>
      </p>
    </prosody>
  </voice>
  <voice name="en-IN-NeerjaNeural">
    <prosody rate="medium">
      <p>
        Andy Morling, head of the MHRA's criminal enforcement unit, explains that this is a new and unusual production model.
        <break time="400ms"/>
        These gangs are investing heavily in <emphasis>designing sophisticated packaging and branding</emphasis>, making their illegal products appear genuine.
        <break time="800ms"/>
      </p>
    </prosody>
  </voice>
  <voice name="en-IN-PrabhatNeural">
    <prosody rate="medium">
      <p>
        Morling noted that while they looked like genuine medicines, they were <emphasis>entirely unlicensed and illegal to sell in the UK</emphasis>.
        <break time="350ms"/>
        In a recent raid on an illegal factory in Northampton, the MHRA seized tens of thousands of empty weight-loss pens.
        <break time="850ms"/>
      </p>
    </prosody>
  </voice>
  <voice name="en-IN-NeerjaNeural">
    <prosody rate="medium">
      <p>
        They also confiscated over 2,000 already filled, unlicensed pens, preventing them from reaching the market.
        <break time="300ms"/>
        Morling emphasized that public safety is their top priority in every case.
        <break time="650ms"/>
      </p>
    </prosody>
  </voice>
  <voice name="en-IN-PrabhatNeural">
    <prosody rate="medium">
      <p>
        The agency is taking a proportionate approach to this growing threat, focusing on <emphasis>removing these dangerous products from circulation</emphasis> to protect consumers.
      </p>
    </prosody>
  </voice>
</speak>